who are there, who show real courage, who bring people together, and to nudge our sons to identify with those heroines and to say, "I want to be on their team," because they're going to be on their team. When I asked my daughter who her favorite character was in "Star Wars," do you know what she said? Obi-Wan. Obi-Wan Kenobi and Glinda. What do these two have in common? Maybe it's not just the sparkly dress. I think these people are experts. I think these are the two people in the movie who know more than anybody else, and they love sharing their knowledge with other people to help them reach their potential. Now, they are leaders. I like that kind of quest for my daughter, and I like that kind of quest for my son. I want more quests like that. I want fewer quests where my son is told, "Go out and fight it alone," and more quests where he sees that it's his job to join a team, maybe a team led by women, to help other people become better and be better people, like the Wizard of Oz. Thank you.
que existen, que muestran verdadero valor, que reúne a personas, y alentar a nuestros hijos a identificarse con las heroínas y decir: «Quiero estar en su equipo» porque van a estar en su equipo. Cuando le pregunté a mi hija cuál era su personaje favorito de «Star Wars» ¿Saben lo que respondió? Obi-Wan. Obi-Wan Kenobi y Glinda. ¿Qué tienen en común estos dos? Tal vez no es solo el vestido brillante. Creo que son expertos. Creo que estas son las dos personas en esas películas que saben más que nadie, y les encanta compartir sus conocimientos con otras personas para ayudarlas a alcanzar su potencial. Ellos son líderes. Me gusta ese tipo de historias para mi hija, y me gusta ese tipo de historias para mi hijo. Quiero más historias como esa. Quiero menos historias en las que se le diga a mi hijo: «Ve y lucha solo» y más historias donde se vea que su trabajo es unirse a un equipo, tal vez un equipo liderado por mujeres, ayudar a otras personas a mejorar y ser mejores personas, como el mago de Oz. Gracias.